本字幕由高清电台整理发布，更多高清电影请访问
https://gaoqing.fm
很长很长一段时间，
For a long, long time,
外星人把他们的罪犯关在人体内。
aliens have kept their criminals locked up in human bodies.
但人类却不知道。
But humans were unaware.
可以随意进出人类的外星人
The aliens that could enter and exit humans at will
被称为帕罗。
were called Paro.
在那里!
Up there!
杀了它!
Kill it!
在那里!
Over there!
天开了……
The heavens have opened...
病例编号78247 - 268万亿年已经过去了。
Case number 78247 - 268 trillion years have elapsed since awakening.
有人员伤亡。
There have been human casualties.
我们得在他们逃到另一具尸体里之前抓住他们。
We have to catch the prisoner before they escape into another body.
跟踪它的位置。
Track its location.
犯人在逃跑。35米。
Prisoner is on the move. 35 meters.
30米。
30 meters.
囚犯正在接近。
Prisoner is approaching.
别担心。
Don't worry.
我安然无恙。
I am unharmed.
我没有问。
I wasn't asking.
它要回到自己的身体里了!
It's returning to its body!
开始提取。
Commencing extraction.
我们会继续来。
We'll keep coming.
我不是最后一个。
I'm not the last one.
你保护的混蛋,
You guard bastards-
你完蛋了。
You're done for.
任务完成。
Mission complete.
回到基地。
Return to base.
我的宝贝…请救救她……
My baby... please save her...
哦!
Oh!
一个婴儿!
A baby!
我们不介入人类事务。
We don't get involved in human affairs.
我听说。“对不起，但我们不参与。”
I've heard that. 'I'm sorry, but we don't get involved.'
坚持下去。
Hang on.
我要开枪!
I have to shoot it!
你是说射击吗?一个婴儿?
Did you say shoot? A baby?
不!
No!
这人类的混蛋…
This human bastard...
犯罪中。
Criminal contained.
等等，我们不带走孩子?它可能会死!
Wait, we're not taking the baby? It could die!
没有干扰。你不明白吗?
No interference. Can't you understand that?
不,来吧。
No, c'mon.
我们不想要个孩子吗?
Don't we want a baby?
你为什么每次都这么做?
Why do you do this every time?
为什么?
Why?
害怕它会取代我?
Scared it'll take after me?
等一下。
Wait a minute.
宝宝……在未来…
The baby... in the future...
别告诉我她出现在你的幻象里。
Don't tell me she's in one of your visions.
我们走吧。门正在关上。
Let's go. The door is closing.
那我想我们得回去了。
Then I guess we've got to get back.
你能做什么?
What can you do?
你为什么坐在后面?
Why are you sitting back there?
啊，我这样太高了，对吧?
Ah, I'm too tall like this, right?
现在离开!
Now departing!
这些外星囚犯跨越时空存在过，
These alien prisoners have existed across time and across space,
守卫和雷霆的工作就是管理他们。
and it was Guard and Thunder's job to manage them.
到目前为止，有七名帕罗逃脱，
So far, there have been seven escaped Paro,
七次成功的遏制。
and seven successful recontainments.
但那天有点不同。
But that day was a little different.
什么?
What?
这是什么?
What is this?
对吧?这里怎么会有个婴儿?
Right? Why would there be a baby here?
我说，这是什么?
I said, what is this?
最重要的是-那个-
The most important thing is that- That-
问题是-是-
See, the thing is- Is-
这是- - - - - -
It's-
你要去哪里?
Where do you think you're going?
不,我不是
No, I'm not-
我为什么要去别的地方?
Why would I be going anywhere?
你为什么把它带来这里?
Why did you bring it here?
看来我们得把它放回去了。
Looks like we'll have to put it back.
还是……我们应该杀死它吗?
Or... should we kill it?
杀了它吗?你为什么不把它留下?
Kill it? Why didn't you just leave it?
啊，我为什么要这么做?
Ah, why have I done this?
啊哈。
Aha.
我提议做个实验!
I propose an experiment!
如果我们检查它的大脑是不是很疯狂…
Wouldn't it be so wild if we examined its brain...
对人类有了更多的了解?
and learned more about humans?
然后……
So then...
首先,我们应该……
First, we should...
第一位?什么?
First? What?
．.． 把它带回家?
... bring it into the house?
我吗?
Me?
是的!
Yep!
这些东西吃什么?
What do these things eat?
婴儿喝母亲产的奶。
Infant humans drink milk produced by their mothers.
主要成分是乳糖脂蛋白。商店里出售替代配方奶粉。
Primary ingredient is lactose lipoprotein. Substitute formulas are sold in shops.
我们要检查宝宝的大脑吗?
Well, shall we examine the baby's brain?
为什么不呢?我们用完就可以扔掉了。
Why not? We can just discard it when we're done.
正确的。当然。
Right. Of course.
准备传播。
Prepare for transmission.
7847号案件，第七次越狱，成功破案。
Case number 7847, the seventh prison breakout, successfully resolved.
分析正在进行中的地球社会。
Analysis of the Earth society in progress.
在某些情况下，人类的大脑可以拒绝我们植入的记忆。
There are cases where human minds can reject our implanted memories.
很有可能人类比我们预期的要复杂得多。
There is a high possibility that humans are more complicated than we anticipated.
嘿。
Hey.
我们还要在这里待多久?
How much longer do we have to stay here?
该信息并未提供。
That information is not provided.
下一批囚犯车队预计将在10年零8个月后抵达。
The next prisoner convoy is expected to arrive in ten years and eight months.
的传播。
End of transmission.
十年零八个月。
Ten years and eight months.
Aigoo。
Aigoo.
你曾把手伸进瀑布升起的水雾中吗?
Have you ever put your hand into the mist rising from a waterfall?
啊，所以就像……你能闻到水的味道吗?
Ah, so it's like... you can smell the water?
嗯。
Hm.
这是无稽之谈。
That's nonsense.
就像我说的，当你把手伸进雾里，
As I was saying, when you put your hand in the mist,
哪里是空气的尽头，哪里是水的起点?雾和你的手成为一体。
where does the air end and the water begin? The mist and your hand become one entity.
的主人。
Master.
我们来演示一下。
Let's have a demonstration.
这不是一个人能真正证明的事情，但是…
It's not something that one can really demonstrate but...
随着古老的Dosa艺术，
With the ancient art of Dosa,
Mureuk甚至可以召唤风!一个动作，他
Mureuk can even summon the wind! With one motion, he-
我不想让前来赏樱的人失望……
I don't want to disappoint the people who came out to see the cherry blossoms...
但我也不能让我的顾客失望。
but I can't disappoint my customers either.
当你像我一样先进时，你对任何伤害都免疫。
And when you are as advanced as I, you are immune to injury of any kind.
任何形式的吗?
Of any kind?
是的。
Yes.
在这里。拿着这个，就在这里
Here. Take that, and right here-
那我可以这么做了?
So I can do this, then?
刀? ?
A knife??
你都没有犹豫，你就
You didn't even hesitate, you just-
手帕。汉-汉
Handkerchief. Han- Han-
我要把它拿出来!
I'll take it out!
不,不,
No, dont-
我说,不!
I said, don't!
它很好。
It's fine.
紧急!村子里有贼!
Emergency! Thieves in the village!
嘿!你是说镇上有赏金猎人吗?
Hey! Did you say there were bounty hunters in town?
在这里!在这里!
Over here! Over here!
他会为你抓住它们的!
He'll catch them for you!
这些是男人吗?
Are these the men?
哦,是的!
Oh, yes!
让我们开始工作吧。我们去抓小偷吧?
Let's get to work. Shall we catch some thieves?
三个人在跑步。
Three men are running.
有一个钟。
There's a bell.
附近有神社吗?
Are there shrines nearby?
这种方式!
That way!
你在逃避什么?
What are you running from?
善良。就因为它在那里，并不意味着你可以偷走它。
Goodness. Just because it's there, doesn't mean you can steal it.
想想你的下辈子。那你也想这样生活吗?
Think of your next life. Do you want to live like this then, too?
我希望你们能从中吸取教训，成为对社会有贡献的一员。
I hope you can learn from this and become a productive member of society.
那是什么?
What was that?
那么。看来我们要去填满一笔赏金了。
Well then. Looks like we're about to fill a bounty.
看，是那个养猫的Mureuk。
Oh look, it's that Mureuk guy with the cats.
放下你的东西!
Lay down your goods!
在这个美好的日子里，我们要伸张正义。
We will be enacting justice on this beautiful day.
制定正义是谁?
Who's enacting justice?
我都已经在这了，你说要拿赏金是什么意思
What are you saying about filling bounties when I'm already here and-
不，拜托，谁先找到赏金谁就有权利，对吧?
No, come on now, whoever gets their sights on a bounty first has dibs right?
不是这样吗?
Isn't that so?
我有权要求这个-
I have a claim to thi-
把自己捆好。现在。
Tie yourselves up properly. Now.
前提是你想让你的耳膜完好无损。
That is, if you want your eardrums intact.
你们从哪里来的?
Where did you guys come from, anyway?
啊,?
Aw, again?
我告诉你，这赏金是我的。
I'm telling you, this bounty is mine.
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
你来了。
Out you come.
是这样的吗?
Was it like this?
你是在模仿江原的古老传统吗?如果你学了一百年，你不可能
You presume to imitate Gangwon's ancient traditions? If you studied for a hundred years, you couldn't-
悬赏三贼，成功填满。
Bounty for three thieves, successfully filled.
嘿Mureuk !
Hey Mureuk!
看一看新上市的产品!
Take a look at the new listings!
让我们看看…
Let's see...
我们下一个要抓什么样的混蛋?
What kind of bastard should we catch next?
肯定有人要出高价。
Definitely someone going for a high price.
真是一群笨蛋。
What a bunch of louts.
看看这个。
Look at this one here.
这是一个生来就是罪犯的女人的脸。
That's the face of a woman born to be a criminal.
50公益诉讼?
50 pil?
二十多岁
Twenty-
不，200 -等等，不
No, two hundred- Wait no-
二千公益诉讼?
Two thousand pil?
等等，我在b-的地方见过
Wait, I've seen this somewhere b-
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
你又头痛了吗?
Do you have another headache?
这个描述太生动了，真的让我觉得我亲眼见过。
This description is just so vivid, it really makes me feel like I've seen it myself.
啊,那个。
Ah, that one.
你知道现在谁在公共场合酗酒，对吧?
And you know who's in for public intoxication right now, right?
我们开始吧~
Here we go~
我要去看狗屎。
Gotta go see Dogturd.
主人，你知道狗屎在哪儿吗?
Do you know where Dogturd is, Master?
也许值得谈一谈。
Might be worth talking to.
你不担心。
Don't you worry.
我很了解狗屎。
I know Dogturd well.
Aigoo,我的主。
Aigoo, my lord.
这个可怜的混蛋来见他亲爱的父亲，狗屎。
This poor bastard has come to see his beloved father, Dogturd.
欢迎的人。
Greet the man.
他可怜的父亲要把自己喝死。
His poor father is going to drink himself to death.
啊,这是什么?
Ah, what's this?
是我们尊敬的礼物。
A gift of our esteem.
请喝一口，先生。
Have just a sip, sir.
哦，看起来是很好的东西……
Oh, it looks like very fine stuff...
如此甜美!
So sweet!
过瘾!
Hits the spot!
既然你把这个带来了，你可以在走之前给你父亲喝一杯。
Since you brought this here, you can take a cup in to your father before you go.
我可以吗?
Can I?
你的好意一定会得到回报的。
Your kindness will surely be rewarded.
你儿子来看你了!
Your son is here to see you!
他一直在哭。
He's crying and everything.
我有个儿子?
I have a son?
父亲……
Father...
你儿子穆鲁克来见你了。
Your son Mureuk is here to see you.
Mureuk，你这个混蛋
Mureuk, you bastard -
你应该羞于在我面前露面，你这个偷东西的混蛋!
You should be ashamed to show your face around me, you thieving bastard!
你再多说一个字，我就
If you say another word, I'll -
他见到他是多么高兴啊!这样的欢迎!
That's how happy he is to see him! Such a welcome!
你说得太伤人了，神父。
That's a lot of hurtful words, Father.
关于这个你能告诉我些什么?
What can you tell me about this?
你觉得我会告诉你吗?
Do you think I'd tell you?
即使我信任你，你也不能给我足够的条件让我开口。
Even if I trusted you, you couldn't offer me enough to get me to talk.
在我杀了你之前滚出去!
Get out of here before I kill you!
那我猜我父亲不想要这把钥匙。
Then I guess my Father doesn't want this key.
啊，我亲爱的儿子!
Oh, my beloved son!
来看望他生病的父亲……
Come to his ailing father...
跟我说说这把刀。
Tell me about the knife.
我来告诉你我知道的。
I'll tell you what I know.
8月5日，在黄岭山附近的渔网中出现了一把奇怪的刀。
On August fifth, a strange knife came up in a net near Mount Hwangnyeong.
它的刀刃上镶嵌着一颗奇怪的宝石。
It had a strange jewel for a blade.
起初，他们想卖掉珠宝……
At first, they had thoughts of selling the jewel...
但即使是铁匠也无法将它与剑柄分开。
But even the blacksmith couldn't separate it from the hilt.
当刀反弹到人群中时，它击中了一名男子，本应杀死他。
When the knife ricocheted into the crowd, it struck a man and should have killed him...
但他站了起来，好像毫发无伤!
But he got up as if he was unharmed!
这肯定是一件珍贵的文物，必须加以保护!
Surely this is a precious artifact that must be protected!
你不觉得吗?
Don't you think?
那现在谁拿着刀?
Then who has the knife now?
这是-
Well, that's -
这是很久以前一位黄陵县长买的。
It was bought by a man who was a Hwangneung magistrate a long time ago.
但现在，它属于一个在启城的男人。
But nowadays, it belongs to a man in Gyeseong.
他经营着一个叫碧南亭的地方。
He runs a place called Byeoknanjung.
啊，这太令人兴奋了。
Ah, this is all very exciting.
你儿子现在可以自己出去了。
Your son will see himself out now.
小心些而已。
Be careful.
他是全国最好的Dosa。
That man is the best Dosa in the country.
说实话，一个前地方法官能做多好的Dosa ?
How good a Dosa could an ex-magistrate be, honestly?
哦，我的父亲，如果你能改变你的方式…
Oh, my father, if only you could change your ways...
你已经很久没有和另一个Dosa对抗了。
It's been a long time since you've gone up against another Dosa.
我不知道你能不能比得上他。
I wonder if you'll be a match for him.
我可能缺乏正规训练
I may lack in formal training,
但我有工作经验。每一天!
but I've got on-the-job experience. Every day!
实用知识胜过书本知识。每个人都知道。
Practical knowledge beats book learning. Everyone knows that.
我看起来像不像上流社会的人?
Don't I look like a man at the top of the game?
上面-你真的这么想吗?
The top- Do you really think that?
毕竟，你是那个粉丝的合法主人!
After all, you're the rightful owner of that fan!
不是吗?你怎么什么都没说?
Aren't you? Why didn't you say anything?
我们跟踪你是因为你说你是风扇的主人。
We're only following you because you said you were the owner of the fan.
仔细想想，你还没拔出那把大剑呢。
Come to think of it, you've still never drawn the great sword.
你以为我不会拔剑吗?嗯?
You think I can't draw the sword? Huh?
你是这么想的吗?
Is that what you think?
我要拔出剑，然后你们都会后悔的!
I'm gonna draw the sword and then you're all gonna be sorry!
我真的在做!
I'm really doing it!
在这里,我们走吧!
Here we go!
他真的做到了!
He's really doing it!
今天的一天!
Today's the day!
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
你看到了吗?你看到了吗?
You see this? You see it?
似乎沉重。
Seems heavy.
下一个时间。
Next time.
周围人太多了。
Too many people around.
这是正确的。不想吓到任何人。
That's right. Don't wanna startle anyone.
我越来越怀疑你不是我们真正的主人。
I'm becoming more and more suspicious that you aren't actually our rightful owner.
如果你还这么顶嘴，我就把你变回猫。
If you're going to talk back this much, I'll just turn you back into a cat.
别这样。让我们人类。
Don't be like that. Leave us human.
人类是谁?
Who's human?
坐下来。
Sit down.
我们快喝一杯吧。
Let's have a quick drink.
我们要点菜，女士!
We'd like to order, ma'am!
在我看来，无论如何你都会占地方法官的上风!
The way I see it, you'll get the upper hand on the magistrate no matter what!
女士，碧南亭在哪里?
Ma'am, where is Byeoknanjung from here?
走那条路，它就在前面。
Go that way and it's straight ahead.
那是谁?
Who's that?
我以前从没见过这样的衣服。
I've never seen clothes like that before.
对吧?
Right?
(BYEOKNANJUNG)
[BYEOKNANJUNG]
我什么都能干!
I'm good for anything!
他得到它!
He got it!
我能和你们两位谈谈吗?
Can I speak with you gents for a moment?
我听说这里有个人曾经是地方法官。
I heard there was a man here who used to be a magistrate.
你认识他吗?
Do you know him?
我听说过那个风扇。你可以给它出个价。
I've heard of that fan. You can name your price for it.
这个啊?
Ah this?
这是一个传家宝。这对我来说是无价的。
It's an heirloom. It's priceless to me.
很多人在这里吃饭……
Lot of people eating here...
偷来的东西怎么可能是传家宝?
How can something be an heirloom if you stole it?
像一个懦夫。
Like a coward.
你该庆幸我能对长辈好点。
You're lucky I have to be nice to my elders.
你不能随便指责别人偷东西!
You can't just go around accusing people of stealing things!
嘿,你这个混蛋!
Hey, you bastard!
我们不允许你们这种人进来!
We don't allow your kind in here!
法官……
The magistrate...
不要在室内，谢谢。
None of that indoors, thank you.
这不是体力的问题，这是意志力的问题。
This isn't about physical strength, this is about force of will.
你不能想，所以你不能做。
You can't think it, so you can't do it.
什么是废话?
What nonsense is -
你认识我吗?
Do you know me?
我了解你这样的人。
I know men like you.
停止追逐赏金，诚实地生活。
Stop chasing after bounties and live honestly.
你们可以回去吃饭了，先生们。
You can get back to your meals, gentlemen.
帮我……
Help me...
的帮助!
Help!
我们的客人到了吗?
Has our guest arrived?
是的。还有你要的信息。
Yes. And the information you asked for.
为什么这么难?
Why is this so difficult?
他的名字没有列出来。
His name isn't listed.
你说你知道这是什么。
You said you know what this is.
我当然知道。
Of course I know.
你是怎么知道的?
How did you learn of it?
因为它是我们的。
Because it's ours.
我们的吗?
Ours?
是的。
Yep.
那是谁?
And who is that?
裁判官去哪儿了?
Where did the magistrate go?
法官吗?他在楼上。
The magistrate? He's upstairs.
他好像认识你。
It seemed like he knew you.
我吗?我这辈子都没见过他。
Me? I've never seen the man in my life.
你看到他了吗?看起来像狗屎。
Do you see him? That looks like Dogturd.
Dogturd吗?
Dogturd?
你是对的。我能闻到他的味道。
You're right. Ugh, I can smell him.
他一定是在找那把刀。
He must be after the knife.
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
在。的。风。的。的。风!
In. The. Wind. Of. The. Wind!
你疼吗?
Are you hurt?
这把刀……不要醒来…
The knife... Don't awaken...
不,
Don't -
你在做什么
What do you m-
我想狗屎把它偷走了!
I think Dogturd's stolen it!
我看你在这儿吃得不错。
I see you eat well here.
你给他看!
You showed him!
你好吗?
You good?
我没事，我没事。
I'm fine, I'm fine.
你又偷了那把刀，对吧?
You stole that knife again, didn't you?
不是那样的!
It's not like that!
走吧!快跑!
Go! Run!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
他在这里，他在这里!
He's here, he's here!
主人,主人!
Master, master!
Mureuk !
Mureuk!
醒醒吧!
Wake up!
他去了哪里?
Where did he go?
我们得找到那把刀。
We've got to find that knife.
这很有趣。他怎么这么对你的?
Well this is interesting. How did he do this to you?
狗屎又跑了。
Dogturd made a run for it again.
你还好吗?
Are you alright?
我想我的背扭伤了。
I think I threw my back out.
为什么我的脸颊会痛?
Why does my cheek hurt?
你打我了吗?
Did you hit me?
我吗?
Me?
他。我为什么要那么做?
Noooo. Why would I do that?
嘿,哇!你看到了吗?
Hey, wow! Would you look at that?
这是什么?
What is this?
是石头吗?
Is it a stone?
什么样的石头会那样发光?
What kind of stone shines like that?
不管是什么，看起来像钱。
Whatever it is, it looks like money.
它一定是由于干旱而浮出水面的。
It must have surfaced because of the the drought.
-它在发出噪音。-嘿，那边有人。
- It's making a noise.  - Hey there's someone over there.
我们打电话给你是因为伊安出了点问题。
We called you because there's a problem with Yian.
她最近去了警察局，想举报你。
She recently went to a police station and tried to report you.
当警察问她为什么来的时候，
When the police asked why she'd come,
她说你绑架了她，
She said that you had kidnapped her,
还有从那以后你一直在扰乱她的记忆，等等。
and that you had been messing with her memory since then, and so on.
好吧，让我们来放磁带。
Well, let's just play the tape.
我们直接从局里拿到的。
We got it straight from the station.
你爸爸为什么要玩弄你的大脑?
Why does your father play with your brain?
他是医生吗?
Is he a doctor?
不,女士。
No, ma'am.
老实说，他不是我父亲。
Honestly, he's not my father.
他是一个机器人。
He's a robot.
像cyborg。
Like a cyborg.
这是令人兴奋的。
Well, that's exciting.
你怎么知道你爸爸是机器人?
And how can you tell your father is a robot?
这是个好问题。你看，我昨天拍了一个视频
That's a good question. You see, I took a video yesterday-
因为有时候他不是我爸爸，他是雷霆。
Because sometimes he's not my dad, he's Thunder.
所以我怀疑,
So I doubted-
雷是谁?
Who's Thunder?
他是我父亲开的车
He's the car my father drives,
但有时他会变成我父亲。
but sometimes he changes into my father.
我记得他们带走我的时候。
I remember from when they took me.
他们已经把视频删掉了。
Oh, they've already erased the video.
我应该更小心的。
I should have been more careful.
我再看一段视频，然后回来。
I'll get another video and come back.
她离开车站来到学校。你是怎么想的?
And she left the station and came to school. What are your thoughts?
抹去局里的录像。
Wipe the video from the station.
它已经完成了。
It's already done.
那个女人一直在监视你。小心些而已。
That woman's been watching you. Be careful.
哪一个?
Which one?
直走。
Straight ahead.
下午!
Afternoon!
你一定在等奕安!
You must be waiting for Yian!
我Minsun的姑姑。
I'm Minsun's aunt.
我明白了。
I see.
敏孙和怡安真是好朋友!
Minsun and Yian are such good friends!
可能是因为他们都不擅长踢足球吧。
Probably because they're both so bad at soccer.
我打赌他们会成为一辈子的朋友!你不这样认为吗?
I bet they'll be lifelong friends! Don't you think so?
确定。
Sure.
你想喝点咖啡吗?
Would you like some coffee?
我在学校见过你几次，
I've seen you around the school a few times,
所以我觉得我应该自我介绍一下!
so I figured I should introduce myself!
你多大了?你有房产吗?
How old are you? Do you own any real estate?
我阿姨觉得你爸爸很帅。
My aunt thinks your dad is handsome.
他是。
He is.
所以我才长得这么帅。
That's where I got my good looks.
但是我们能做什么呢?
But what can we do?
我爸爸不喜欢她。
My dad doesn't like her.
他看起来像是在玩躲避球。
He looks like he's playing dodgeball.
她会没事的。看她。
She'll be fine. Look at her.
她是一个永不放弃的女人。
She's a woman who never gives up.
阿姨!
Auntie!
嘿Minsun !
Hey Minsun!
啊，原来你是易安!你这么漂亮!
Ah, so you're Yian! You're so pretty!
你的帅气是遗传你爸的吗?
Did you get your good looks from your dad?
这是我自己做的。
These are a little something I baked up myself.
这是给你和依安的!
These are for you and Yian!
他们非常好。
They're shockingly good.
开车安全。
Drive safe.
我们走吧!
Let's go!
凯。
Kay.
什么?
What?
校长说了什么?
What did the principal say?
你不好奇我今天和朋友们做了什么吗?
Aren't you curious what I did with my friends today?
不,我不是。
No, I'm not.
啊。我明白了。
Ah. I see.
谢谢你载我一程，雷霆。
Thanks for the ride, Thunder.
你在跟谁说话?
Who are you talking to?
给他。
To him.
汽车不能说话。
Cars can't talk.
雷声。当我小的时候。
Thunder used to. When I was little.
我记得。
I remember.
你的日子不多了…
Your days are numbered...
你和她谈过了吗?
Have you been talking to her?
一个字也没有。
Not a word.
我是说，她年轻的时候我是这么做的。
I mean, I did when she was younger.
她还记得那件事吗?
Does she remember that far back?
但雷是什么?
But what's Thunder?
那是我的名字吗?
Is that my name?
放弃它。
Quit it.
很奇怪的东西。
Something's weird.
你话太多了。
You talk too much.
为什么会被抹去?我的名字?
Why would that have been erased? My name?
把报告给我。
Just give me the report.
报告:第19个囚犯车队。高级帕罗斯岛。
Report: Nineteenth prisoner convoy. High-ranking Paros.
将抵达地球进行植入。107例。
Will arrive on earth for implantation. 107 subjects needed.
植入?那是什么?
Implantation? What's that?
的位置。
Location.
我仍然搜索。
I'm still searching.
我们需要107个人类宿主。车队预计十八小时后到达。
We'll need 107 human hosts. Convoy estimated to arrive in eighteen hours.
18小时。这是明天。
Eighteen hours. That's tomorrow.
每天晚上9点，我父亲就消失了，
Every night at 9 o'clock, my father disappears,
所有的灯都熄灭了。
and all the lights go out.
在这里。
There it is.
雷声!
Thunder!
对我来说太好了?
Too good for me?
我明白了。
I see how it is.
看来我得自己去找答案了。
Guess I gotta get all my answers myself.
那是什么?
What is that?
不喜欢。
Don't.
嗯?
Huh?
不喜欢。
Don't.
别碰!
Don't touch that!
雷声。
Thunder.
从我小的时候。
From when I was little.
但是…为什么我的名字叫雷霆?
But... Why is my name Thunder?
你不喜欢吗?
You don't like it?
我已经习惯了。
I'm getting used to it.
很好。
It's good.
那么，你到底是什么人?
So, what exactly are you?
你从哪里来?
Where did you come from?
对于你的第一个问题，我是一个程序，
For your first question, I am a program,
它可以处理数据并改变其物理形式。
that processes data and can vary its physical form.
你想要什么?
What would you like?
你的爸爸?
Your dad?
但是…你不是…
But... you're not...
你是全息影像吗?
Are you a hologram?
不,我是真实的。我真的在这里。
No, I'm real. I'm really here.
我甚至曾经抱过你。
I even used to hold you.
你问我来自哪里!
You asked where I'm from!
你大老远从那里过来的?
You came all the way from there?
你和爸爸是外星人吗?
Does that mean you and Dad are aliens?
对我来说，你就是外星人。
To me, you're the alien.
我爸爸是你老板吗?
Is my Dad your boss?
老板?不。
Boss? No.
我们的同志。平等的。
We're comrades. Equals.
我只是把战斗留给他，因为我反对暴力。
I just leave the combat to him because I'm against violence.
你的家很远吗?
Is your home far away?
虽然很远，但不会花很长时间
Well, it's far, but it doesn't take us very long beca-
爱因斯坦。
Einstein.
你快。
You're fast.
你长得这么聪明!
You grew up so smart!
你甚至帮我起了名字。
You even found my name for me.
真的吗?嘿!自动贩卖机里的零食都是你换的!
Really? Hey! You're the one who changes the snacks in the vending machine!
我做!你怎么能吃这么多鱼干?
I do! How do you eat so much fish jerky?
——对吗?和玉米零食!——对吧!
- Right? And corn snacks!      - Right!
明天的植入手术在哪里?
Oh and what and where is the implantation tomorrow?
在医院吗?他们会为囚犯找到尸体的。
Ah at the hospital? They'll find bodies for the prisoners.
植入。
Implantation.
你听到消息了。
You heard the message.
叛徒。
Traitor.
我不是叛徒。我只是想知道
I'm not a traitor. I just wanted to kn-
你爸爸要来了。滚出去!很快!
Your dad's coming. Get out! Quickly!
等等。
Wait.
我从哪里来?
Where did I come from?
我下次再告诉你!你要走了!
I'll tell you next time! You gotta go!
请告诉我!
Tell me, please!
我从哪里来?
Where did I come from?
过去!646年前!
The past! 646 years ago!
忘了我跟你说的医院的事!
And forget what I told you about the hospital!
你必须!
You have to!
你刚才在跟谁说话?
Who were you just talking to?
只是现在吗?
Just now?
有一条新消息。
There's a new message.
移植将在距离这里8公里的济桑医院进行。
implantation will take place 8 km from here, at Jisang Hospital.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我很好。
I'm fine.
你在拍什么?
What are you filming?
我只是喜欢记录人物。
I just like making records of people.
你永远不知道什么时候会失去记忆。
You never know when you'll lose your memory.
你有点病态。
You're a little morbid.
你会忘记什么事情?
What kinds of things do you forget?
没有什么,但是……你永远不会知道的。
Nothing yet, but... you never know.
坚持下去。
Hang on.
如果发生什么事，给我打电话，好吗?我是一个警察。
If anything happens, call me, okay? I'm a cop.
通过。
Pass.
你们看到了吗?它是漂亮!
Do you see that? It's pretty!
营救囚犯的准备工作已经完成。
Preparation for prisoner extraction is complete.
是什么-
What is-
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
我来这里干什么?
What did I come in here for?
可怜的人。
Poor man.
哦，多么惨痛的损失……
Oh, what a devastating loss...
我们还有很多事要谈。
We had so much left to talk about.
这是我第一次见你这样。
This is the first time I've seen you like this.
我告诉过你拿刀的是他，不是吗?
I told you he was the one with the knife, didn't I?
你所做的。
You did.
是另一个人偷的!
And that other man stole it!
一个犯罪!
A criminal!
他会是什么样的多萨?
What kind of Dosa could he be?
首先,
First of all,
我敢肯定他不是Dosa。
I feel certain he isn't a Dosa.
小偷在这里。有什么锋利的东西穿墙而入，把门撞得粉碎。
The thief was here. Something sharp went through the wall and and smashed the door.
也许是偷来的东西?
Maybe the stolen item?
不知怎么的，我不这么认为。
Somehow, I don't think so.
一个触手?
A tentacle?
在这里吗?
Here?
偏偏是这里?
Here, of all places?
我的心比赛。
My heart races.
和我们看到的那个一样吗?
Is it like that thing we saw-?
我想是的。
I think so.
你还记得吗?
Do you remember?
那个一直住在米尔本的人。
That man who's been living in Milbon.
是的，我想我们应该去拜访他。
Yes, I think we should pay him a visit.
我想我们应该。
I think we should.
你是…三岳山的法师?
Are you... the mages of Samgak mountain?
正确的。
Correct.
你卖那些小饰品?
And you sell the trinkets?
小饰品吗?你听到了吗?
Trinkets? Are you hearing this guy?
镇上的人说这个人已经在这里住了十年了!
The people in town said this guy has lived here for ten years!
他是个非常稳重的人
He is extremely dan-
你真的要进去吗?
Are you actually going in?
是的。
Yeah.
不去看，或者
Not gonna check it out or-
在神庙中找到神圣之剑，并把它带到约定的地点。
Locate the Divine Sword in the temple and bring it to the agreed-upon location.
找到什么?
Locate what?
什么?
The what?
你觉得是米尔本的神庙吗?
Do you think it's the temple at Milbon?
是他们点的吗?
Are they the ones ordering this?
他们为什么要找同一把刀?
Why would they be looking for the same knife?
哇。这幅画很奇怪。
Whoa. This picture is strange.
那是什么?
What is that?
哦!
Oh!
为什么我觉得我以前见过这个方形的东西?
Why do I feel like I've seen this square thing before?
这么说住在这里的人真的是疯了。
So the guy who lived here was actually just crazy, then.
在哪里可以看到这些奇怪的东西?
Where could someone see all these weird things?
为了能够敲开这扇美好的门，我们走了很长的路。
That was an awfully long way to come, just to be able to knock on this fine door.
我真希望他没去别的地方。
I sure hope he hasn't gone anywhere.
根据你告诉我的，那不是他的风格。
From what you told me, that doesn't seem to be his style.
我听说他自从十年前来到这里就没出过这扇门。
I heard he hasn't stepped foot outside these gates since he arrived here ten years ago.
你认为他是什么样的人?
What kind of person do you suppose he is?
让我们尽我们所能卖掉这些小饰品，看看我们能不能弄明白。
Let's sell our little trinkets as hard as we can and see if we can figure that out.
三阁山的法师来了，大人。
The mages of Samgak mountain have arrived, my lord.
天哪，是他自己。
Goodness gracious, the man himself.
他见到我们非常高兴。我透过他的面具都能感觉到。
He's overjoyed to see us. I can feel it even through his mask.
所以你是对的。
You're so right.
你们就是我听说过的不可思议的法师。
So you're the incredible mages I've heard so much about.
感谢您的光临。
Thank you for gracing me with your presence.
如果我们听说密尔邦对我们的货物有兴趣，我们当然要马上赶来。
If we hear that Milbon has interest in our wares, of course we must come right away.
让我们给你看看我们能提供什么。
Let us show you what we can offer.
的事情
things
到目前为止，我们提供给米尔邦的产品与我们今天带给您的产品相比，显得苍白无力。
The products that we have offered Milbon so far pale in comparison to the wares we bring you today.
例如，这个护身符……
For example, this talisman...
能让我同时出现在两个地方。
can allow me to be in two places at once.
密切关注。
Watch closely.
看来这不是你要找的东西。
Ah, I see this is not what you're looking for.
我们试试别的吧。
Let's try something else.
不要去任何地方。
Don't go anywhere.
我已经追上你了。
I have caught you fast.
如果您愿意从我们这里购买一件，我将再买一件以示感谢。
If you are so kind to purchase one from us, I will add a second one in gratitude.
我明白了。
I see.
在这里!我们有这面宏伟的铜镜!
And here! We have this magnificent bronze mirror!
其他镜像根本无法与之相比。
Other mirrors can simply not compare.
一个不诚实的人看着这面镜子，会发现自己的不诚实被放大了十倍。
A dishonest man can look into this mirror and see his dishonesty magnified tenfold.
我能看到自己的美丽和纯洁。
And I can see my own beauty and purity.
你想看一看吗?
Would you like to have a look?
在密尔本，我们自己的外表并不重要。
In Milbon, our own appearances are of no importance.
你真聪明。
How wise of you.
但镜子的放大率也有其他用途。
But the mirror's magnifying powers can be of other uses as well.
有了它的帮助，小事情不必再小了。
With its help, small things don't have to be small.
整个聚会只要喝一杯就足够了。
Just one drink can become enough for an entire gathering.
在战斗中，一个小拳头就可以变成一支军队。
And in a fight, just one small fist can become an entire army.
看着我的手。
Keep your eyes on my hand.
好了，开始。
Alright, here we go.
哦，我一这么做就会有大麻烦了。
Oh, there's going to be big trouble as soon as I do this.
我想我们已经给他看得够多了。
I think we've shown him enough.
我很惊讶仅仅是人类就能做出如此非凡的产品。
I'm amazed to hear that mere humans could make such extraordinary products like this.
是的，我们不是很了不起吗?
Yes, aren't we quite remarkable.
这。
And this.
无价的阿拉伯磨刀石。
A priceless Arabian whetstone.
即使成千上万的士兵每天使用这块石头，它也需要15年才能开始磨损。
Even if thousands of soldiers used this stone every day, it would take 15 years to begin to wear away.
这刀刃可以用三年。
The blade's edge will hold for three years.
仔细想想，它是无价的。
It's priceless when you think about it.
但如果你要给它定价的话…
But if you had to put a price on it...
至少70 pil。
70 pil, at least.
嗳哟!
Oho!
如果你不感兴趣的话就没必要提这个。
Ah, there's no reason to bring that up if you're not interested.
有什么发现吗?
Did you find something?
如果贵方第一眼不能被我们的商品所吸引，就没有必要向贵方推销。
If you are not charmed by our wares on first glance, there is no point in selling them to you.
看看那家酒吧还在不在这附近。
Let's see if that bar is still around here.
都这么久了，我真的在想…
It's been so long, I really wonder...
浪费会议时间。
Waste of a meeting.
你们俩真的知道神刀在哪里吗?
Do the two of you really know where the Divine Knife is?
当然。
Of course.
北村，在一个企业主的手中。
Bukchon, in the hands of a business owner.
至少是这样。
Or it was, at least.
不幸的是，被一个叫狗屎的人偷走了。
Unfortunately, a man named Dogturd stole it.
米本有什么办法能帮你找到它吗?
Is there any way that Milbon can assist you in finding it?
咔咔。
Ho ho.
一个很好的问题。
An excellent question.
这些混蛋知道他们在干什么吗?
What do these bastards think they're doing?
哦，新郎确实是个很好的人。
Oh, the groom is a very fine man indeed.
留着漂亮的小胡子。你看到那胡子了吗?
And sporting a fine mustache. Did you see that mustache?
什么?下马。
What? Dismount.
把你的胡子借给我。
Lend me your mustache.
我的-我的胡子?
My- My mustache?
是的。
Yep.
他在这里。他在这里!
He's here. He's here!
新郎到了!
The groom has arrived!
新郎是一个真正的男人!
The groom is a real man!
大家快围过来!
Everyone gather 'round quickly!
你觉得它在那边吗?
Is it over there, do you think?
我不确定。
I'm not sure.
新郎新娘齐聚一堂!仪式开始!
The bride and groom are gathered! Let the ceremony begin!
让我们第一次一起喝一杯吧!
Let's share our first drink together!
嗯。先做什么?
Um. What comes off first?
我的新娘……
My bride...
.．.是美丽的。
...is beautiful.
但是…
But...
我们以前是不是在什么地方见过?
Haven't we met somewhere before?
这是不可能的。
That's impossible.
如果我们只是——
What if we just-
摆脱,
Get rid of-
这是什么?
What is this?
这没什么好担心的。
It's nothing that you need to concern yourself with.
我们先喝一杯好吗?
Shall we start with a drink?
当然。做一下。
Sure. Let's do that.
我们不应该让主人好好享受一下吗?
Shouldn't we let our master enjoy himself?
我们还有工作要做!我们不能玩变装游戏!
We have work to do! We can't be playing dress-up!
荒谬。
Ridiculous.
哦，看，他们在蒸鱼!
Oh look, they steamed fish!
这还不是季节呢!
It's not even in season!
这宝贵的东西…
This precious stuff...
第一次……
First...
一个小零食。
A little snack.
是的，只会一点。
Yes, just a little.
不是春天，不是……
It's not spring, no...
但这种鱼在秋天会更好吃!
But this fish is even better in the fall!
我认为你是对的。
I think you're right.
啊，等一下。我有些事要处理。
Ah, just one second. I need to take care of something.
我简直不敢相信。
I can't seem to believe it.
我嫁给了像你这样的人。
That I've married someone like you.
他很可爱。
He's cute.
你为什么这么坚持?
Why are you being so insistent?
我得确保它不在里面!
I had to make sure it wasn't in there!
主人，我们听说在家里的仓库里，在墙那边。
Master, we heard it's in the family storehouse, over that wall.
我明白，我明白。
I get it, I get it.
你喝酒吗?
Were you drinking?
我刚生了一个小孩。
I just had a little one.
什么-
What-
我是怎么了?
What's happening to me?
我们是三岳山的双重法师。
We are the dual mages of Mount Samgak.
谁也不许离开这房子。
No one leaves this house.
把你仓库里的东西拿来，别惹麻烦。
Bring us the contents of your storehouse and don't cause any trouble.
我们得到了密尔邦的多萨的帮助…
We are aided by the Dosa of Milbon...
所以如果你想看到早上就不要越过那条线。
So don't cross that line if you want to see morning.
立即阻止他们!
Stop them immediately!
你知道你在干什么吗?
What do you think you're doing?
我不知道你在这里做什么
I don't know what the hell you're doing here
但你得在…之前滚出我家
But you get out of my house bef-
你的意志就是我的意志。
Your will is mine.
是的。
Yes.
你的意志就是我的意志。
Your will is mine.
把你隐藏的东西带给我。
Bring me what you've hidden.
你的意志就是我的意志。
Your will is mine.
把你隐藏的宝藏带给我。
Bring me your hidden treasures.
是的。
Yes.
你说的任何东西。
Anything you say.
Aigoo。
Aigoo.
我的夫人!你在这里做什么?
My lady! What are you doing here?
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
Eunnie, Eunnie !
Eunnie, eunnie!
他们把我捆成这样!
They tied me up like this!
但如果你在这里…那谁结婚了?
But if you're here... then who got married?
对不起，让你久等了
Sorry to have kept you waiting-
马上把神圣之刀给我拿来!
Bring the Divine Knife to me immediately!
等等，你不是-你不是真正的新娘吗?
Wait, are you- Are you not the real bride?
看来你也不是真正的新郎。
Seems like you're not the real groom, either.
等待……
Wait...
你给我下药了吗?
Did you drug me?
是的。
Yeah.
“是的”?
'Yeah'??
你不会死的。别担心。
You won't die. Don't worry.
解药。
Antidote.
一定有解药。
There must be an antidote.
没有。
There isn't.
没有吗?
There isn't?
睡一觉就好了。你会没事的。
Just sleep it off. You'll be fine.
我来对付那些混蛋。
I'll take care of those bastards.
我是唯一能做到的人。
I'm the only one who can.
你有这个。
You've got this.
你能做到的。
You can do it.
你是…
You are...
你疯了!
Out of your mind!
我知道我不是真正的新娘，
I know I'm not the real bride,
但我会非常怀念今天。
but I'll remember today very fondly.
待在原地别动!
Stay where you are!
啊，原来是把枪。
Ah, so that's a gun.
没关系。
It doesn't matter.
把那个给我。
Give that to me.
是的,女士。
Yes, ma'am.
不要动。
Don't move.
顺便说一下…你擅长解谜吗?
By the way... how are you at solving puzzles?
这很清晰。
That's very sharp.
噢,那刺!
Ow, that stings!
我有她!
I've got her!
把那女孩带过来。
Bring the girl with us.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
Mureuk !
Mureuk!
他是来。
He's coming to.
按摩他，按摩他。
Massage him, massage him.
那个女人是从哪里来的?
Where did that woman come from?
我想问她的，但是
I tried to ask her that, but -
新郎在里面。
The groom is inside.
我们走吧。
Let's get out of here.
嘿,那件事。
Hey, that thing.
砰砰的枪声!抓住它!
The bang-bang! Grab it!
砰砰的枪声?这- - - - - -
The bang-bang? This -
什么?这是什么?
What?  What is this?
砰砰的枪声是什么?
What's a bang-bang?
嗨,燕。
Hey, Yian.
你为什么没去上学?
Why weren't you at school?
我离家出走了。
I ran away from home.
我今晚可以留下来吗?
Can I stay over tonight?
哦我的上帝!这真的是我们的医院吗?
Oh my God! Is this really our hospital?
这是你自己拍的?
And you filmed this yourself?
正确的。
Right.
他们脑子里想的是什么?
What are those things going into their heads?
你爸爸也是那样的人吗?
Is your dad one of those things?
嘘。
Shh.
阿姨吗?
Auntie?
嗯?
Huh?
我什么都没做。
I'm- I'm not doing anything.
我只是路过。自然。
I'm just passing by. Naturally.
我消失……
I'm going away...
我们从敏生家来的。
We've arrived in from of Minsun's house.
我从来不知道该对人类说什么。
I never know what to say to humans.
你去代替。
You go instead.
我吗?
Me?
我应该用什么外观?
What appearance should I use?
我!我会做的!接我!
Me! I'll do it! Pick me!
我一直想说服一个人类!
I've always wanted to persuade a human!
你跟人类说过话吗?
Have you ever spoken to a human?
你没有，是吗?
You haven't, have you?
我只是在等待合适的机会。
I'm just waiting for the right opportunity.
我对人类略知一二。
I know a little bit about humans.
我去。
I'll go.
不要着急。
Hold your horses.
你知道怎么勾引女人吗?
Do you know how to seduce a woman?
你们俩有谁跟他们说过话吗?
Have either of you ever talked to one?
深情地说，眼神交流，问问题，抱着她的腰。
Speak deeply, make eye contact, ask questions, hold her waist.
你有这方面的经验吗?
Do you have any experience in these things?
那我们三个都去吗?
Should we all three go then?
不。只有一个人。只有一个。
No. Just one of you. Just one.
你这样做。
You do it.
尽量简短。
Just keep it short.
燕。
and get Yian.
这就是精神。
That's the spirit.
好吗?
Shall we?
让我们偷一些心吧。
Let's steal some hearts.
哦,你好…
Oh, hello...
你就在那里。
There you are.
所以。
So.
啊，你是来接依安的吗?
Ah, did you come to get Yian?
这不是显而易见的吗?
Isn't it obvious?
我知道你对我有兴趣。
I know that you're interested in me.
我是谁?
I am?
你。
You are.
我想知道我能不能找个时间给你打电话。这样可以吗?
Ah, I had wondered if I could call you up sometime.  Is that alright then?
是的。
Yes.
你绝对应该这样做。
You should definitely do that.
那么，我应该叫怡安吗?她在楼上。
Should I get Yian, then? She's upstairs.
我宁愿和你继续聊。
I'd rather keep talking to you.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
啊，我是闵桂仁。(听起来像“外星人”)
Ah, I'm Min Gye-in. (sounds like 'alien')
我已经知道了。
I already know.
我妈为什么这么叫我，对吧?
Why would my mom call me that, right?
我取了很多绰号。好。基本上就是《异形，异形》。
I've picked up a lot of nicknames. Well. Mostly just 'Alien, Alien.'
Minsun !
Minsun!
分钟Gye-in小姐。
Miss Min Gye-in.
关于你…
The thing about you...
你是如此幸运…
Is you're so lucky...
你不是外星人。
You're no alien.
你真好。
Very kind of you.
Welp。让我们出去。
Welp. Let's head out.
医院里的那些人是怎么了?
What went into those people at the hospital?
我在问你问题!
I'm asking you a question!
哦,她是疯了。
Ooh, she's mad.
你还不了解人类吗?
Do you still not understand humans?
向他们隐瞒事情是没有意义的。
There's no point in trying to hide things from them.
燕。坐,坐。
Yian. Sit, sit.
那些人是怎么了?
What went into those people?
然后。我们会回答你三个问题。
So then. We will answer exactly three of your questions.
好吧?如此!
Okay? So!
那些人是怎么了?
What went into those people?
啊,,。
Ah, that.
所以问题是…
So the thing is...
很长一段时间以来，我们一直把地球上的囚犯锁在人类的身体里。
for a really long time we've been locking up our planet's prisoners in human bodies.
对吧?
Right?
停止。
Stop.
不，我来吧。
No, I've got this.
每个星球都是一样的，对吧?有文明，有战争，有人口下降……
Every planet is the same, right? There's civilization, there's war, there's a decline in population...
但每个人都想要和平。
But everybody wants peace.
我们当然也有罪犯。
We have criminals like anybody else, sure.
但是一个全新的问题出现了。
But then a whole new problem appears.
我们的种群开始变异。
Our population starts mutating.
生活与和平颠倒了!
Life and peace turned upside down!
突变如此强大，他们可以摧毁和杀戮。
Mututions so powerful they can destroy and kill.
然后呢?
Then what?
所以你需要一个监狱。
So then you need a prison.
你必须把他们带到很远的地方，让他们永远不会回来。
You have to take them so far away that they can never come back.
这是最难以进入的地方。
The most impenetrable place there is.
一个连监狱长都不记得的监狱。
A prison that even the wardens won't remember.
人类的心灵。
The human mind.
把罪犯放进去
Put a criminal in there,
他们被困住了，直到那个人死了把他们俩都毁灭。
And they're trapped, until the human dies and destroys them both.
我们就是这么做的。
That's how we do it.
但我们还没同意。
But we haven't agreed to this.
未经允许进入我们的大脑?
Going into our brains without permission?
我们为什么需要许可?
Why would we need permission?
你不应该那样对待别人。
You shouldn't treat people like that.
人类物质。
Humans matter.
你长得这么聪明!
You grew up so smart!
这是你最好的特点。
It's your best trait.
闭嘴。
Shut up.
下一个问题。
Next question.
这些罪犯能离开他们的身体吗?
Can these criminals leave their human bodies?
有一点，但这里的气氛不同。
For a little bit, but the atmosphere is different here.
大概五分钟?
About what, five minutes?
是的。他们可以在外面待那么久。
Yeah. They can stay out for about that long.
如果他们醒了，我就把他们困起来藏起来。
If they awaken, I trap and store them.
在哪里?
Where?
这里。
Here.
后面有房间吗?
There's a room back there?
如果他们唤醒……
If they awaken...
人受伤?
People get hurt?
这就是我要阻止的。
That's what I'm here to prevent.
所以你是在保护我们。
So you're protecting us.
我是看守囚犯的。
I'm a Guard who manages prisoners.
人类与我无关。
Humans are not my concern.
提问时间结束。
Question time is over.
那你为什么养我?
Then why did you raise me?
提问时间结束。
Question time is over.
我今晚可以睡在这里，对吗?
I can sleep here tonight, right?
谢谢。
Thanks.
你来地球多久了，雷?
How long have you been on Earth, Thunder?
你一直都在这里吗?
Have you always been here?
你为什么带我来?
Why did you bring me with you?
如果我们不这么做，你早就死了。
If we didn't, you would have died.
睡个好觉,燕。
Sleep tight, Yian.
晚安,雷声。
Good night, Thunder.
嫌犯朝你方向去了。
Suspect is heading toward you.
操作开始。
Operation commencing.
你在干什么?稍等!
What are you doing? Hold the line!
别在这里!
Stop right there!
这是警察骚扰，你知道的。
This is police harassment, you know.
啊，太浪费了。
Ah, what a waste.
别拍我!不要开枪!
Don't shoot me! Don't shoot!
谢谢你所做的一切。
Thank you for everything.
嘿,月亮Doseok。
Hey, Moon Doseok.
是的。
Yeah.
你以为你在干什么，向平民开枪吗?
What do you think you're doing, shooting at a civilian?
只是对罪犯开了一枪以示警告。
Just a little warning shot at a criminal.
嘿。
Hey.
下次，你应该打我。
Next time, you should hit me.
侦探从来没有完成过任务。
Detectives never get the job done.
原谅我们。
Excuse us.
剩下的呢?
Where's the rest of it?
我把它藏在阁楼的自行车里了。
I hid it in the bike in the loft.
阁楼里的自行车?
The bike in the loft?
想去玩个开心的夜晚吗?
Wanna go have a fun night?
哈!
Ta-da!
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
去看看吧。
Go check it out.
曹先生吗?
Mr. Cho?
新消息传入的。
New message incoming.
越狱的囚犯向地球进发。
Escaped prisoners headed for Earth.
武装和危险。
Armed and dangerous.
获取与护理。
Capture with care.
你是说有武器吗?
Did you say armed?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
紧急消息!
Emergency message!
紧急营救一名囚犯!
Urgent recovery of a prisoner required!
我们到底该抓谁?
Who exactly are we supposed to catch?
这个混蛋!他是医院里的囚犯之一!
This bastard! He was among the prisoners from the hospital!
了他!发现了这个混蛋!
Got him! Found the bastard!
他在这里。
He's here.
名称:月亮Doseok。
Name: Moon Doseok.
尸体是在楼梯间被发现的，我们正试图获取监控录像。
The bodies were found in the stairwell, and we're trying to obtain the CCTV.
我们已经把这把斧头上的样本送去鉴证了。
We've sent samples from this hatchet off to forensics.
警探不接电话。
The detective isn't answering his phone.
燕出去。
Yian, get out.
不。
No.
我要看看你和雷霆在做什么。
I'm going to see what you and Thunder are doing.
出去。
Get out.
我不出去了。
I'm not getting out.
我是你的家人。这也是我的事。
I'm your family. It's my business too.
紧急通知!
Urgent message!
那艘船-那艘船正在接近那颗行星!
The ship- The ship is approaching the planet!
然后抓住。
Then hold tight.
没办法及时开车去那里。
There's no way to drive there in time.
然后我们会飞。
Then we'll fly.
爸爸，这是什么?
Dad, what is this?
坐下。
Sit.
月亮DoSeok。
Moon DoSeok.
你在哪里?
Where are youu?
别插手。
Stay out of this.
文多锡的位置在哪里?
What is Moon Doseok's location?
21楼。的电梯。
Twenty-first floor. By the elevator.
那东西要追上他了。
That thing is catching up to him.
月亮DoSeok。
Moon DoSeok.
我们的控制者被锁在你体内了。
Our controller has been locked inside you.
谁-
Who -
我必须把控制器从你的人体中解放出来。
I must free the controller from your human body.
我会用守卫的能量来做到这一点。
I will use the Guard's energy to do so.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
文都石的帕罗是谁?
Who's the Paro in Moon Doseok?
囚犯#197A:控制者。
Prisoner #197A: The controller.
控制器吗?
The controller?
就是破坏我们星球的那个人。
The same agent of the destruction on our planet.
叛乱的领袖
The leader of the rebellion.
你觉得他们打算逃跑吗?
Do you think they're planning to escape?
或者他们想要别的东西?
Or do they want something else?
那是什么鬼东西?
The hell is that?
控制器，能听到我说话吗?
Controller, can you hear me?
你准备好获得自由了吗?
Are you ready to be set free?
地球的大气层发生了变化。
The earth's atmosphere has changed.
是时候解放他们了。
It is time to free them all.
我们就从你开始。
And we will begin with you.
的时间……是现在。
The time... is now.
这个混蛋在说什么?
What is this bastard saying?
燕,我们开始。
Yian, we're starting.
雷声,做好准备。
Thunder, get ready.
依安，抓紧了!
Yian, hold on tight!
把能量转移到武器上。
Divert energy to weapons.
水平!
Levels up!
我们有他!
We've got him!
还没有。我们刚刚给了他翅膀。
Not yet. We've just winged him.
武器!
Weapons up!
武器达到最高水平!
Weapons to their highest level!
小心!他就在我们后面!
Careful! He's right on our tail!
分析的弱点!
Analyze weak points!
只有一个入口可以进入内部系统。
There's only one point of access to the interior systems.
那鲜红的部分就像它的心脏!
That bright red part is like its heart!
直接击中它，你就能破坏它们的力量!
Hit it directly, and you can disrupt their power!
它每次射击都会打开!
It opens every time it shoots!
我们在交火中抓到人类…
We're catching humans in the crossfire...
我们找个干净的地方!
Let's get somewhere clear!
准备好了…
Ready...
集……
Set...
火!
Fire!
它的心感动!
Its heart moved!
屏蔽耗尽。
Shield depleted.
我们被击中了!
We've been hit!
崩盘迫在眉睫。
Crash is imminent.
更多的能量!
More energy!
我需要更多的时间!我需要更多的时间!
I need more time! I need more time!
任务完成。
Mission complete.
控制器被唤醒。
The controller is awakened.
控制器空闲。
The controller is free.
现在我要自我毁灭…
And now I will self-destruct...
带你一起走。
And take you with me.
警告:守卫的生命维持系统已启动。
Warning: Guard's life support activated.
能源枯竭!
Energy depleted!
燕!
Yian!
在车里等着!
Wait in the car!
能量水平为17%。
Energy levels at 17%.
16%。14%。
16%. 14%.
达到临界水平。
Reaching critical levels.
开始紧急充电。
Beginning emergency recharge.
紧急充电正在进行
Emergency recharge, in progress.
36%。
36%.
38%。
38%.
我的储备已经耗尽了。
My reserves are depleted.
控制器被唤醒。
The controller is awakened.
我们需要更新状态。
We need a status update.
理解。
Understood.
尽量不要动!
Try not to move!
控制器可以进入飞船。
The controller has access to the ship.
Haava。
Haava.
It's Haava.
他们把它带到这个星球上!
They brought it to this planet!
Haava吗?从我们的世界远道而来?
Haava? All the way from our world?
地球的大气层太不一样了!
Earth's atmosphere is too different!
如果他们能部署哈瓦人
If they can deploy the Haava,
它们将能够永久地改变地球的大气层!
They'll be able to change Earth's atmosphere permanently!
他们不再需要人类的身体了。
They won't need human bodies anymore.
他们都可能被唤醒!
They could all be awakened!
如果这个被释放了
If this is released,
所有的人类都会死在新的大气层里。
all the humans will die in the new atmosphere.
这是真正的…最后。
This is truly... the end.
我们必须关掉控制器!
We have to stop the controller!
使用能量刀破坏部署!
Use the energy knife to disrupt the deployment!
能量水平又下降了!
Energy levels falling again!
阻止哈瓦人是最重要的。
Stopping the Haava is the important thing.
出去抓住控制器
Go out and catch the controller
在他跳进另一个身体之前!
before he can jump into another body!
易安，你还好吗?
Yian, are you okay?
那是什么东西?
What is that thing?
这就是我们在这里的目的。
That's what we're here for.
我没看到控制器。
I don't see the controller.
上车。
Get in the car.
状态报告。
Status report.
两剂哈瓦烟已经离开飞船。
Two doses of Haava have left the ship.
我会尽量控制住他们。
I'll try to contain them.
首先找到控制器。不能让他引爆它们。
Find the controller first. He can't be allowed to set them off.
Haava引爆。
Detonate the Haava.
呼叫所有帕罗人。
Calling all Paro within range.
苏醒了。
Awaken.
睁开你的眼睛!醒醒吧!
Open your eyes! Wake up!
皮带-我不能-
The belt- I can't-
他们只注射了一剂哈瓦烟!
They've deployed one dose of Haava!
先拯救人类!
Save the humans first!
我要!
I'm going!
燕,我们走吧。
Yian, let's go.
我要送你回家。
I'm sending you home.
雷声!
Thunder!
我必须拯救你的世界。
I have to save your world.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我必须找到控制器。
I have to find the controller.
那些死去的人…
The people who died...
那朵明亮的哈瓦云…
That bright cloud of Haava...
那一天我无法忘记，即使十年后……
That day I couldn't forget, even ten years later...
你是谁?
Who are you?
你已经长大了。你忘了我吗?
You've grown up. Did you forget me?
我们一起来的，你知道的。十年前。
We came here together, you know. Ten years ago.
我会继续找那把刀的。
I'll keep trying to get that knife.
确定。
Sure.
你也需要我们骑过来的那辆车。
You need that thing we rode here, too.
在哪里?
Where is it?
不晓得。
Dunno.
真的吗?我知道。
Really? I know.
所以我才需要那把刀。
That's why I need that knife.
在哪里?
Where is it?
是时候让你尝尝监狱里的滋味了。
It's time you learned what it's like to be in a prison.
我们有时间。想想你将如何在这样的混乱中生存下来。
We've got time. Think about how you're going to survive the mess you're in.
先生。
Mister.
你走之前为什么不吃顿饭呢?
Why don't you have dinner before you go?
像你说的。我们有时间。
Like you said. We've got time.
我们被困在时间里了。
We've been trapped in time.
我们必须在回去之前找到控制器。
We have to find the controller before we go back.
他一定是改变了身体
He must have changed bodies,
但是法官并没有被唤醒。他刚刚去世。
but the magistrate wasn't awakened. He just died.
那控制者会在谁的身体里?
So whose body could the controller be in?
那天有四个人看到了我们。
Four humans saw us that day.
裁判官死了。两个法师都被刀割了，但他们也没有被唤醒。
The magistrate died. The dual mages were both cut by the knife, but they were not awakened either.
现在我们必须找到最后一个。
Now we must only locate the last one.
它很好。
It's fine.
她既听不到也说不出我们的秘密。
She can neither hear nor speak our secrets.
你为什么还呆在这么虚弱的身体里?
Why are you staying in such a weak body?
换一下不是更好吗?
Wouldn't it be better to switch?
我会喜欢我的回忆。
I'll love my memories.
如果我不想再被关起来，我需要
And if I don't want to be imprisoned again, I'll need-
Mureuk吗?
Mureuk?
你还好吗?
Are you alright?
进密尔本大学不是很困难吗?
Isn't it going to be too difficult to get into Milbon?
困难吗?
Difficult?
为我们吗?
For us?
看看这个。如果我们能填满这一份，那么…
Look at this. If we can just fill this one bounty, then...
这将解决我们所有的问题。
This will solve all our problems.
你觉得这是什么?
What do you think it is, anyway?
很明显是很重要的事情。
It's obviously something important.
有可能像你一样英俊聪明吗?
Is it possible to be as handsome and smart as you are?
他是最聪明的!最帅!
Just the very smartest! Very most handsome!
你不认识我吗?
Don't you know me?
他们的到来。
They're coming.
我们可以开始工作了吗?
Shall we get to work?
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
你怎么这么晚才来?
Why are you so late?
你找到了吗?
Did you find it?
他们在等你。我们走吧。
They're waiting on you. Let's go.
正确的。
Right.
你还能再快一点吗?
Are you going to move any faster than that?
我们匆匆。
We're hurrying.
你要去哪里?
Where do you think you're going?
对的,正确的。
Right, right.
哦，药在这里。
Oh, the medicine is here.
我们找到药了，伟大的法师们。
We have found the medicine, great mages.
那一定是难以捉摸的。
It must have been elusive.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
给它。
Give it here.
你听说过他。
You heard him.
致命的蘑菇…
That deadly mushroom...
彻底咀嚼它。
Chew it thoroughly.
你们谁是解药专家?
Which one of you is the antidote expert?
我们的解药专家……
Our antidote expert...
这个人在吗?
Is this man here.
正确的。
Right.
专家。
Expert.
快点。咀嚼它。
Hurry. Chew it.
不要停止咀嚼。
Don't stop chewing.
麦芽浆。
Mash it up.
放点口水进去。
Get some saliva in there.
就是这样，就是这样。
That's it, that's it.
现在，你为我带来了什么。
And now, what you have brought for me.
这个吗?
This?
在这里,随地吐痰。
Here, spit.
你嚼得很好。
You chewed it very effectively.
这艘船在碧南井附近的山谷中浮出水面。
The ship has surfaced in the valley near Byeoknanjung.
我们有它。
We've got it.
为什么刀现在有反应了?
Why is the knife reacting now?
它自己就亮了!
It's lighting up all on its own!
完全靠自己?一定很特别!
All on its own? It must be special!
这是停止了。
It's stopped.
为什么这么多人在找这个小东西?
Why are so many people looking for this little thing?
即使今天受了那么多次伤，
Even after getting injured so many times today,
你还是不能管好自己的手。
you still can't keep your hands to yourself.
她只是想知道。
She was just wondering.
正确的。只是思考。
Right. Just thinking aloud.
我今天不再需要你的帮助了。
I will not be requiring your services any further today.
走之前吃点晚饭。
Have some dinner before you go.
你们三个在干什么?
What are you three doing?
我很想知道这里还发生了什么。
I'd be very interested to know  what else is going on around here.
你看到刀了吗?
Did you see the knife?
我们晚上再来吧。
Let's come back at night.
很明显。
Obviously.
钱跟我们的一样好。
The money is as good as ours.
你。
You.
把这个。
Take this.
把它交给后面的女孩，然后马上回来。
Give it to the girl out back and return immediately.
别跟她说话。
Don't speak to her.
欢迎加入！
Yessir.
你们两个。洗碗。
You two. Wash the dishes.
回来吗?
Out back?
那是哪儿?
Where is that?
多么美好的一天。就连鸟儿也这么认为。
Such a beautiful day. Even the birds think so.
让我们看看，让我们看看。
Let's see, let's see.
哦,我明白了。
Oh, I see.
这里有一个小间隙。
And a little gap here.
他们是怎么做的?
How did they make this thing?
是火灾引起的吗?
Does the fire cause it?
那么。
Well then.
哦，这没什么用。
Oh, that didn't do anything.
该死的。
Darn.
嘿。
Hey.
你就是那个小偷吗?
Are you that thief?
小偷吗?这是严酷的。
Thief? That's harsh.
在我给你带晚餐之后。
And after I brought you dinner.
那朵花我也要吃吗?
Am I supposed to eat the flower too?
你为什么要这么做?
Why would you do that?
所以你甚至会为了生存而吃花。
So you'll even eat flowers to survive.
这么勇敢的女孩怎么会被关在这里?
How did such a brave girl wind up locked up out here?
和你的理由一样。
Same reason as you.
你不是来拿刀的吗?
Aren't you here for the knife?
当然不是。我就住在那边。
Of course not. I live right over there.
你偷了吗?
Did you steal it yet?
不,还没有。
No, not yet.
但就在我出来之前，
But just before I came out here,
我看到它开始发光
I saw it start glowing
伴随着美丽柔和的蓝光。
With this beautiful, soft blue light.
它照亮了吗?在你面前?
It lit up? In front of you?
事情发生的时候我就在那儿，但是-
I was just there when it happened, but -
但是等待。
But wait.
我真的觉得我是在年轻的时候遇到你的。
I really feel like I met you when I was younger.
但这是雾蒙蒙的。
But it's foggy.
如果你想告诉我你喜欢我，请别这样。
If you're about to tell me you like me, please don't.
我们并没有真正结婚。
We're not really married.
不,听。我真的觉得如果我能记得那天……
No, listen. I really feel like if I could just remember that day...
帮我记住。
Help me remember.
你来自哪里?
Where are you from?
你怎么来的?
How did you get here?
你真的需要我的人生故事吗?
Do you really need my life story?
小偷先生，你的生活离我远远的。
Mr. Thief, just live your life far away from me.
诚实地谋生。
Earn an honest living.
我就知道你会这么说。
I knew you'd say that.
那么，这有什么意义呢?
Now, what is the significance of this?
这是从哪里来的?
Where did this come from?
雷声是怎么来的?
How does the thunder come out?
不要拉!
Don't pull that!
把它给我，小心点。
Give it to me, carefully.
首先，告诉我这把刀是从哪来的。
First, tell me where the knife came from.
从未来。(未来)
From the future. (mirae)
未来吗?
Mirae?
等等，我也经历过。月清里附近
Wait, I've been there. That neighborhood by Wolcheongni -
不，那不对。
No, that's not right.
这是Miorae。
That was Miorae.
那我还没去过。
I haven't visited, then.
我来自600多年后的未来。
I came here from over 600 years in the future.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think of that?
所以我今天也得不到你的任何答复。
So I'm not getting  any answers from you today, either.
哇。“你觉得怎么样?”板着脸问。
Wow. "What do you think of that?" with such a straight face.
你得编个比这更好的谎话才能摆脱我。
You'll need a better lie than that to get rid of me.
你是说你住在那里。在未来。
So you're saying you live there. In the future.
是的。
Yep.
明白了吗?
Does that make sense?
等待。等等，放手，着火了
Wait. Wait, let go, there's fire -
把枪给我。
Give me my gun.
火!我着火了!
Fire! I'm on fire!
热了!
Hot!
那个人在哪里?
Where is that man?
我会还给你的，但我想我会先把刀拿回来。
I'll give it back,  but I think I'll get the knife first.
你在跟谁说话?
Who were you talking to?
我们走吧。
Let's go.
[裁判官的记录]
[THE RECORD OF THE MAGISTRATE]
这个女孩吗?
The girl?
她吃了食物。
She ate the food.
她现在死了。
She's dying now.
埋葬她。
Bury her.
把他们埋在一起。
Bury them both together.
理解。
Understood.
把刀。
Bring the knife.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
你知道我们有多久没吃米尔本的食物了吗?
Do you know how long it's been  since we ate Milbon's food?
十年吧，我想。
Ten years, I think.
我们先吃吧
Let's eat first and -
毒……的食物吗?
Poison... in the food?
那是谁?
Could it be?
让我们迅速行动。
Let's move quickly.
在石化开始之前。
Before the petrification sets in.
的解药,很快。
The antidote, quickly.
僵化的
The petrification
是多少。这里。
Is.  Here.
快点,快点。
Hurry, hurry.
快，快，快，快。
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
拉,拉。
Pull, pull.
食物。毒药。
Food. Poison.
一个。Ti。溺爱。
An. Ti. Dote.
解药?
Antidote?
棺材是
Coffins are coming
什么。棺材吗?
What. Coffins?
我们的!棺材!
Our! Coffins!
你是谁?
And who are you?
食物中有毒物。
Poison in the food.
食物有毒?
Poison in the food?
食物中有毒物。
Poison in the food.
但我给了她一些食物。
But I gave her some of that food.
的解药。
The antidote.
那只老鼠混蛋。
That rat bastard.
在风中，在风中!
In the wind, of the wind!
如果你不介意的话……
If you'll excuse me...
主人!
Master!
得到他。
Get him.
森林!
To the forest!
抓住他们!
Catch them!
很热!
It's hot!
它太热了。
It's so hot.
热……
Hot...
你刚刚是在擦嘴吗?
Did you just wipe your mouth?
当然。我就不追究了。
Sure. I'll let that slide.
我们去看看那个混蛋为什么要我们死。
Let's go find out why that bastard wants us dead.
等待- - -
Wait-
我带他们走。
I'll lead them away.
他在那儿!得到他!
There he is! Get him!
抓住他!
Catch him!
我必须回去。
I have to go back.
待在这里。
Stay here.
不，你不能去。
No, you can't go.
那个女人……
That woman...
她可能会死。
She could die.
Mureuk，你也可能会死。
Mureuk, you could also die.
没关系。
It's okay.
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
的解药。
The antidote.
我带了解药。
I brought the antidote.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
是我给你带来毒药的。
I'm the one who brought you the poison.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
你做的很好。
You're doing great.
你会没事的。
You'll be fine.
埋葬的女孩。把那个男孩扔进河里。
Bury the girl. Dump the boy in the river.
准备窑。
Prepare the kiln.
是时候回去了。
It's time to go back.
[不知这神秘的云从何而来…]
[It is not known where the mysterious cloud came from...]
[但我们敦促人们远离首尔的受灾地区。]
[But we are urging people to stay out of the affected areas of Seoul.]
[官员们正在努力评估威胁，但目前还没有具体措施。]
[Officials are trying to evaluate the threat, but there is no word yet on what can be done.]
那是什么?
What's that?
这是我们的能量之源。
This is the source of our energy.
有了这把刀的力量
With the power in this knife,
我们可以抓住逃犯…
we can catch escaped criminals...
我们甚至可以改变时间，看过去。
We can even shift time, and see across it.
对我们来说，它不是线性的。
It isn't linear, for us.
这一切都同时存在。
It all exists at the same time.
当我们带你回来的时候…
When we brought you back...
我们以前就是这么做的。
This is what we used to do it.
如果我回去，就能救人了吗?
Then, if I went back, I could save people?
我不是这个意思。
That's not what I mean.
从某种意义上说，那些人已经死了。
In some sense, those people have already died.
这种能量变得越来越不稳定。
And this energy has become increasingly unstable.
你不知道。
You have no idea.
我看到的未来……是断裂的。不清楚。
The future I see... Is fractured. Unclear.
找到收集器。把这个武器给他。
Find the collector. Give him this weapon.
这里还有人，但他们都漂浮着。
There are people here but- they're floating.
我说，它们在漂浮!
I said, they're floating!
别碰,
Don't touch-
我想我看到我自己…
I think I saw myself...
太久没见了。
It's been too long.
看来你还没有完全恢复体力。
It seems you are not restored to your full strength.
不，我还需要在这张表上多留一段时间。
No, I will need to stay in this form for a little while longer.
恐怕我还不是我自己。
I am not yet myself, I fear.
至少有3名救护车工作人员在大雾中失踪。
At least 3 ambulance workers have been lost inside the fog.
正如你所看到的，它仍然相当厚，所以最好是计划替代路线暂时。
As you can see, it remains quite thick, so it is best to plan alternate routes for the time being.
此外，无人机还拍摄了一些神秘的画面
In addition, drones have filmed some mysterious footage-
这是之前的红色物质，对吧?
That's the red stuff from earlier, right?
人死亡。
People died.
那只是一剂哈瓦。
That was only one dose of Haava.
他们拥有更多。
They have a lot more.
在那艘船吗?
In that ship?
爸爸，你受伤了吗?
Dad, are you hurt?
我很好。
I'm fine.
我得去处理那艘船了。
I have to go take care of that ship.
很危险，我可能不会回来了，所以…
It's dangerous and I might not come back, so...
我要告诉你一件重要的事。
I'll tell you something important.
你的妈妈。
About your mom.
我的妈妈?
My mom?
是我杀了她。
I was the one that killed her.
为什么?
Why?
我需要杀死锁在她体内的东西。
I needed to kill the thing that was locked in her.
我带你来是因为我需要你。
And I brought you here because I needed you.
如果我有个孩子…
If I had a child...
我可以和人类生活在一起而不被发现。
I could live among humans without notice.
但现在你却碍事了。
But now you're getting in the way.
所以我请你离开。
So I'll ask you to leave.
你就是在说谎。
You're lying.
机器人不会说谎。
Robots don't lie.
我去。
I'll go.
我知道你不是人类，但是…
I knew you weren't human, but...
那就把我送回我来的地方。
Then send me back to where I came from.
你的应急储备只剩9%了
Your emergency reserves are down to 9%.
如果我走了，你的存活率
If I leave, your survival rate-
我知道。停止讲话。
I'm aware. Stop talking.
伊安，在外面等一会儿。
Yian, wait outside for a moment.
雷-
Thunder-
带她去明星家。我知道。
Take her to Minsung's house. I know.
你在画上写了什么?
What did you write on the picture?
(跑了,假。)
[Run away, dummy.]
雷声。
Thunder.
替我传达最后的讯息。
Deliver my final message for me.
我们错了。像这样利用人类。
We were wrong. To use humans like this.
但是守卫永远也跑不掉。
But Guards can never run away.
所以即使我没有足够的储备来赢得这场战斗…
So even if I don't have the reserves to win this fight...
我必须遵守我的计划。
I must follow my program.
储备?这是什么意思?
Reserves? What does that mean?
而是他还能活多久。
It's how much life he has left.
他在一点点地消耗。
He's running out, little by little.
现在……外汇储备为8%。
Right now... reserves are at 8%.
生存的机会……
Odds of survival...
1%．
1%.
雷，我们得回去。
Thunder, we have to go back.
我不能。
I can't.
我得带你去安全的地方。
I have to take you to safety.
爸爸需要你。
Dad needs you.
把车掉头。
Turn the car around.
你不可能帮他的。
There's no way you can help him.
也许吧，但我的心告诉我，我们必须试试。
Maybe, but my heart says we have to try.
让我们回到爸爸身边。
Let's go back to Dad.
那这个混蛋在哪儿?
So where is this bastard?
警报已经打开了。
The alarm has been turned on.
我们吃完就走。
We should finish this and go.
你的心吗?
Your heart?
是的。
Yes.
人类的心脏真的很神奇。
Human hearts are really amazing.
为什么?
Why?
战斗成功的几率……
Odds of battle success...
2%．
2%.
3%。
3%.
现在4%。
Now 4%.
准备部署。
Prepare deployment.
校准完成。
Calibrations complete.
我们差不多了。
We're almost there.
你为什么要回来?
Why are you coming back?
那艘船有个弱点…
That ship has a weakness...
内部系统和外部系统之间的联系……
The connection between the inner and outer systems...
那颗红心，记得吗?
That red heart, remember?
你在跟谁说话?
Who are you talking to?
我把刀给你。
I'll get the knife to you.
让它进入心脏。
Get it into the heart.
现在移动。
Moving now.
得到它!
Got it!
原来是你在追我们。
So you're the one who's been chasing us.
一直住在这里…
Living here all this time..
甚至抚养其中一个孩子。
Even raising one of their children.
爸爸!
Dad!
我们走吧，爸爸。
Let's get out of here, Dad.
你为什么回来?
Why did you come back?
雷，你在听吗?
Thunder, are you listening?
在哪里?
Where is it?
爸爸!
Dad!
他们来了!
They're coming!
我们阻止不了他们。
We can't stop them.
他们只会继续追我们。
They're just going to keep chasing us.
爸爸!
Dad!
他在车上!
He's on the car!
我们得在他们释放剩下的哈瓦人之前阻止他们!
We have to stop them before they can release the rest of the Haava!
让我们切换时间。
Let's switch times.
准备好了,…
Ready, set...
走吧!
Go!
原来这是他的房间……
So this was his room...
和他的衣服吗?
And his clothes?
这……你觉得这像是时间记录吗?
Does this... look like a record of time to you?
如果是日历，那一定是3600天左右。
If it's a calendar, it must be about 3600 days.
他在做什么?
What's he been doing?
他在等什么吗?
Is he waiting for something?
Jungmoon Heuksol…这是我们。
Jungmoon, Heuksol... That's us.
那是治安官，那是狗屎…
That's the magistrate, and that's Dogshit...
看这里。他摧毁了一些东西。
Look here. He destroyed something.
高丽六年，黄延道。
Goryeo Year Six, Hwangnyon Province.
这是十年前的记录。
This is a record from ten years ago.
天空打开了。一辆奇怪的马车从天上掉下来，后面拉着人。
The heavens opened. A strange carriage, pulling humans behind it, fell from the sky.
我看到它和地方法官在一起，他在附近打猎……
I saw it with the magistrate, who was hunting nearby...
还有三岳山的双重法师。
And the dual mages of Mount Samgak.
我们在书里。
We're in the book.
十年前
10 YEARS AGO
那是什么?
What is that?
他们通过某种传送门来到这里。
They've come through some sort of portal.
调查它。
Investigate it.
在这儿等着。
Wait here.
我将回来报告。
I'll report back.
我的主人，我的主人!
My lord, my lord!
到底发生了什么?
What on earth is happening?
是很危险的!退后!
It's dangerous! Stay back!
但它就在我们家旁边!
But it's right by our house!
雷声!
Thunder!
我们失去了他们。我们回去吧，雷霆。
We lost them. Let's get back, Thunder.
得……回来……
Gotta... get back...
雷-
Thunder-
雷声!
Thunder!
待在车里。
Stay in the car.
爸爸!
Dad!
雷，带她回去!
Thunder, take her back!
现在就做!
Do it now!
雷声!
Thunder!
爸爸!
Dad!
获胜几率:10%……
Odds of victory: 10%...
15%。
15%.
17%。
17%.
为什么会增加?
Why is it increasing?
我要死了……
I'm dying...
易安会做的。
Yian will do it.
与另一个人。我现在看到了。
With another human. I can see it now.
门关上了。
The door has closed.
燕……
Yian...
你一定要再找到我!
You have to find me again!
我们可以解决这个问题!
We can fix this!
我需要另一个身体……
I need another body...
人类……
Human...
我必须找到一个人类!
I must find a human!
你醒了!
You're awake!
你来自哪里?
Where are you from?
你的衣服真奇怪!
Your clothes are strange!
雷声!
Thunder!
能量-我不能失去-
Energy - I can't lose the -
你看到一个像刀的东西了吗?
Did you see a thing that looks like a knife?
一把刀吗?
A knife?
有什么重要的事吗?
Is it something important?
我去找找看。
I'll go look for it.
待在这里。
Stay here.
谁……
Who...
它不可能是……我……
It can't be... me...
我为什么会在那里?
Why am I there?
这是梦吗?
Is this a dream?
我记得这个。
I remember this.
我在河岸上发现了一个女孩。
I found a girl on the riverbank.
她让我去找把刀。
She asked me to find a knife.
我怎么还活着?
How am I still alive?
你可曾把手…
Have you ever put your hand...
在瀑布升起的薄雾中?
into the mist rising from a waterfall?
她不是,
She's not-
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
我们的转变。
Our turn.
你是困了。
You are sleepy.
你不想躺下吗?
Don't you want to lay down?
你的身体很重……你的眼睛闭上了……
Your body is heavy... Your eyes are closing...
冻结。
Freeze.
我们给你的时候你就该买，你个混蛋。
Should have bought it when we offered it, you bastard.
如果你想瞎，就揉眼睛。
Rub your eyes if you want to go blind.
和下一个……
And next...
我们很高兴向您介绍……
We are pleased to introduce...
你应该买的其他东西。
Something else you should have bought.
我们最新的产品!
Our newest product!
Soorisoori-ma Soorisoori-ma。
Soorisoori-ma, soorisoori-ma.
Soorisoori-ma-ha Soorisoori-ma-ha。
Soorisoori-ma-ha, soorisoori-ma-ha.
是,,
Is that -
这是治安官的剑。
It's the magistrate's sword.
嗯，这个怎么样?的解药。
Well, how about that. The antidote worked.
你不是死了!你还好吗?
You're not dead! Are you okay?
看来你不知道Dosa。
Seems you don't know Dosa.
我会把这个做完的。
I'll finish this one off.
小心些而已。这些混蛋甚至能进入你的身体。
Be careful.  These bastards can even enter your body.
只是为了争取一些时间。
Just buy some time.
嗯。我可以做到。
Hmm. I can do that.
啊。我记得我们以前在哪儿见过
Ah. I remembered where we met befo-
这是一种极好的新产品。我们做得很好。
This is an excellent new product. We did well.
她还活着。
She's still alive.
太好了。
That's great.
为什么我——
Why am I -
我感觉她的痛苦就像我自己的一样。
I'm feeling her pain like it was my own.
因为那是苏阳的女儿。
Because that's Suyang's daughter.
嘿,小子。
Hey, kid.
把这种药敷在你的伤口上。
Put this medicine on your injuries.
抓住。
Catch.
我说出来是因为看起来我们是一伙的。
I'm sharing because  it seems like we're on the same side.
之前的事我很抱歉。
I'm sorry about before.
我相信你是。
I'm sure you are.
我是黑索尔，三岳法师。
I'm Heuksol, of the Mount Samgak mages.
我是燕。
I'm Yian.
多么不寻常的名字。
What an unusual name.
在风中，在风中。
In the wind, of the wind.
最后。
Finally.
帮助她!
Help her!
我要把他关在这里!
I'll hold him here!
这看起来是我的工作!
This looks like a job for me!
热。
Hot.
很热。
Very hot.
Heuk-sol !
Heuk-sol!
他是怎么得到那把剑的?
How did he get that sword?
燕!
Yian!
拍摄,拍摄!
Shoot, shoot!
对着镜子，那儿!
Into that mirror, there!
开枪!
Shoot!
他自由自在!
He's breaking free!
抓住他!
Hold him!
嘿。我就是你要找的人。
Hey. I'm the one you're looking for.
右爪，左爪!跟那个女孩走!
Right Paw, Left Paw! Go with the girl!
完成了。你的五分钟到了。
Done. Your five minutes are up.
有一些…
There's something...
明白了……在你…
Got it... Inside you...
你说什么?
What did you say?
在你…有一些…
In you... there's something...
我里面有什么?
What's inside me?
在你…
In you...
那那那件事……
That... That... That thing...
在你…
In you...
你说什么
What are you sayi-
我没找到刀……
I didn't find any knives...
但这是你的吗?
But is this yours?
是的。
Yes.
你叫什么名字?我Mureuk。
What's your name? I'm Mureuk.
燕。
Yian.
它是什么?
What is it?
外面可能有危险的东西。
There might be something dangerous out there.
我去看看。
I'll go take a look.
不!
No!
别担心。
Don't worry.
我很坚固。
I'm very sturdy.
发现一个…
Found one...
一个人……
A human...
Heuk-seul……早些时候……
Heuk-seul... Earlier...
有四个名字挂在电话上。
There were four names hanging up.
但并不是我们所有人。
But it wasn't all of us.
不四。
Not four.
我们中有五个人看到了他们。
Five of us saw them.
然后……
Then...
所以他们需要找到的最后一个…
So the last one they needed to find...
他拥有Dosa的力量…
He has the powers of a Dosa...
还有他体内的一个怪物。
And one of those monsters inside him.
我们一定要杀了他吗?
Do we have to kill him, then?
我们得在他们释放剩下的哈瓦人之前阻止他们!
We have to stop them before they can release the rest of the Haava!
我们得快点行动!
We have to act fast!
让我们切换时间。
Let's switch times.
那是什么?
What is that?
离爆炸还有48分钟。
48 minutes left until detonation.
控制器被唤醒。
The controller is awakened.
自由的到来。
Freedom is coming.
的时间……
The time...
是现在。02:22:28 000——> 02:22:43 000——M